

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Mathematics. I love the collaborative nature of web development where the philosophy is two heads are better than one, although one works as well! I enjoy creating user-friendly products that have organized, intuitive functionality ensuring a seamless user experience.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Ruby

FRAMWORKS & LIBRARIES: ReactJS, NextJS, Bootstraps, NodeJS, Express, EJS, Ajax, jQuery, Material-UI, Rails

SYSTEMS & DATABASES: PostgreSQL, Git **TESTING:** Jest, Storybook, Cypress, RSpec

PROJECTS

Waxwing Oct. 2022

· React-based app that allows users to view and share recipes for drinks. Users can also create their own recipes.

Tech Stack: React, Express, PSQL, Knex.js, Axios, Bootstrap, Styled Components, Material UI

Wiki-Maps Aug. 2022

- Web application that allows users to collaboratively create maps that list multiple locations. For example: "Best Places to Eat Around Town" or "Locations of Movie Scenes".
- Tech Stack: Express, Node, PostgreSQL, EJS, Ajax, jQuery

Jungle Sept. 2022

- An app built with Ruby on Rails that allows visitors to view, purchase, and review products. Email receipts are sent upon a successful order that uses
 theStripe API for secure transactions.
- Tech Stack: Ruby, Rails, Stripe API, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap CSS

Scheduler Sept. 2022

- · Single-page application that allows students to book and cancel interviews with mentors in real time.
- Tech Stack: React, Axios, Classnames, Normalize, Storybook, Cypress

TinnyApp Aug. 2022

- RESTful URL shortening web application
- Tech Stack: Node, Express, EJS

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs 2022

Diploma Full-Stack Web Development

University of British Columbia Sept. 2014 - June 2020

B.S Combined Major in Math and Science BEd Secondary Math Teacher Education

- CS Courses: CPSC 221-Basic Algorithms and Data Structures, CPSC 210-Software Construction, CPSC 121-Models of Computation, CPSC 110-Computation, Programs, and Programming

EMPLOYMENT

LESSO, Web Developer Intern, China

- · Worked closely with the web team to develop and maintain the eCommerce platforms for the company
- Collaborated with Product Management on new reporting requirements

Phoenix Magnet Academy, High School Math Teacher, Squamish, BC

Learned and mastered new subjects in a short amount of time and successfully delivered lessons

• Designed thoughtful curriculum and lessons that were accessible to all learners and met different needs of students

Sino-Canadian School, High School Math Teacher, Jiangxi, China

Aug. 2020 - June 2021

Aug. 2021 - June 2022

- Regularly met tight deadlines, graded assignments, and created report cards for 60+ students per semester
- Successfully communicated and collaborated with students, parents, and fellow teachers